General Reference; Collection ua950.002
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- J, 1932-1995; 10
  - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Junior and Sophomore Handbook, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Junior Reception, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Juniper House (Cooperative Women's Dormitory), 1932-1942 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- K, 1922-1994; 11
  - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi Fraternity Kappa Rho Chapter, recognized by national 1981 Pan Hellenic Council, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Kappa Beta Fraternity, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kappa Mu, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kappa Phi Kappa, 1922; 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kappa Psi, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Karate Club, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Kate Stoneman - State Normal School, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Kauffman, Larry, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Kelly, Edward F. - Evaluation Conference, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Kelly, Edward F. - Evaluation Conference Proceedings, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Kelly Memorial Fund, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy, John F., Memorial Service, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Kickline, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Kirtland, Richmond H., Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Klub Polski, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Korean Student Association, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Kosher Kitchen - "Research of the Establishment of the Kosher Kitchen at SUNYA"by Samuel Bogen '72 Chairman Kosher Food committee, Jewish Students Coalition, 1968-1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Kosher Kitchen, 1972 September (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Kunitz, Stanley New York State Poet, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- L, 1934-2006; 12
  - Lake House, Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Archives - L.O.A.C. Lake Ontario Archives Conference "Time, People, and Money" 14 - 15 JUN 1996 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Latin American and Caribbean Studies, Department of, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Latin American Coalition of Albany, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Lazarus Cluster (Freedom Quad), 1988 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Learning Center, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Lecture Center, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Lecture Center, Louise De Angelis Hall Dedication (Donated by Sorrell Chesin, 8/28/93), 1992 August 27 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Lecture Center, Edward S, and Francis Gildea George Lecture Center (Donated by Sorrell Chesin, 8/28/93), 1992 August 27 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Lectures, 1971-1977 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Legal Services Office, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Legislative Lecture Series, Undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Paul C. Lemon Award, Undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Leonard, Elmore (author), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Lesbian and Gay Bisexual Alliance, 1994 February (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Lesbian and Gay Center, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Lesbian For Freedom, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Lending and Credit Analysis Program (Office of Public Services), Undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Liberal Education Advancement Program (LEAP), 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Liberal Studies Program Master's in Liberal Studies Program, Undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Liberal Studies Program (Office of Graduate Admission), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Libertarian Alliance, Undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - LibQual+Survey, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - LibQual+Survey, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Librarians, Organization of SUNYA, ca. 1967 June 21-1968 April (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Librarians, Organization of SUNYA, 1969 January 2-1970 March 30 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Libraries - 2 Millionth Book Celebration Gift of Meredith Butler, Undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Libraries: Adopt a Needy Family Project, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Libraries: Chancellor's Award for Excellence in Librarianship, Undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Libraries: Community Conversations, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Libraries - Dewey Library Thomas E. Dewey Graduate Library for Public Affairs and Policy - Program from Environmental Control System Dedication, Undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Libraries - Diversity Committee, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Libraries - Elective Library, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Libraries Faculty Forum, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Libraries: Goals, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Libraries - M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives Invitation to Naming Dedication, 1996 September 27 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Libraries - Historical Childrens' Collection, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Libraries - Informational Guides, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Libraries - Judaica Collections Dedication (Kosover Collection), 1996 May (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Libraries - Organizational Chart, Undated (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Libraries - Progress, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Libraries - Progress Report, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Libraries - Reference Department Meeting Minutes, 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Libraries - Special Collections State University of N.Y. at Albany, ca. 1997 May 27 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Libraries - Strategic Plan Draft, 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Library, ca. 1972 October 21-1985 May (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Library - Acquisitions Department, Undated (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Library - Administrative Group, 1980 December 16-1985 December 3 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Library, Administrative Services, 1973 December 7-1985 May 3 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Library - Affirmative Action, 1973 September 7-1973 September 13 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Library - Alumni Library, Undated (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Library Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Library Annual Reports - Graduate Library for Public Affairs and Policy, 1982 July 15-1985 July 1 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Library Annual Reports - Graduate Library for Public Affairs and Policy, 1986/05/14-1987/06/22 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Library Annual Reports - Graduate Library for Public Affairs and Policy, 1969/10/24-1972/11/22 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Library, Association of Research Libraries Statistics, Undated (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Library, Bibliographers' Meetings, 1982 March 22-1984 December 13 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Library Bibliographers Subject Assignments, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Library, Bibliographic Development Unit Minutes of Meetings, 1973 November 16-1982 March 11 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Library, Bibliographic Development Unit - Miscellaneous, 1973 October 15-1984 December (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Library, Bibliographic Instruction, 1940-1984 April (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Library Bibliographies, ca. 1966 December 6-1972 November (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Library Bibliographies, 1973-1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Library Bibliographies, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Library Browsing Collection, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Library Building and Equipment, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Library Catalogue and Shelf list Maintenance, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Library Circulation, ca. 1934 July 9-1985 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Library - Mary Elizabeth Cobb. Conference Room Dedication, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Library Collection Development, Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Library Collection Development, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Library Collection Development Policies Committee, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Collection Development Division - Academic Faculty Term Renewal Procedures, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Library Commencement, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Library Committee Memberships, 1973; 1975; 1978; 1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Library - Committee on Status of Librarians, ca. 1968 March 4 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Library - Committee on Status of Librarians, ca. 1966 March 21-1967 August 9 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Library - Committee on Status of Librarians, ca. 1967 September-1967 December 21 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Library - Committee on Status of Librarians, 1968 January 4-1968 March 4 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Library - Committee on Status of Librarians, 1968 July 12-1969 June 9 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Library - Communications Projects Librarian, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Library - Computer Search Services, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Library - Countdown Branch, ca. 1967-1972 June 19 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Library - Countdown Branch, 1972 January 20-1978 December 8 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Library - Cyprus Room "Taylor and Edith Belcher Cyprus Room", 1989 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Governor Thomas E. Dewey Graduate Library Dedication Ceremony Gift of Sharon Brook, 1988 September 8 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Library, Dedication, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Library Direct Access Program, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Library, Director's Office, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Library Disabled Services, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Library Disaster Prevention Team/Disaster Action Team, Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Library Discretionary Salary Increases, Undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - "Electronic Information Access Technologies: A Faculty Needs Assessment" by Judith A., Deborah L., Sharon C., Sue R. Faerman, Thomas J. Gavlin, 1993 March (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Library, Evaluation, 1975 January-1975 July; Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Library, Exhibits, 1973; 1984 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Library, External Newsletter, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Library, Fact Sheet, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Library, Faculty and Staff, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Library Faculty, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Library Faculty By - laws, 1970 January 8-1974 August (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Library Faculty By - laws, 1974 September 5-1982 April 6 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Library Faculty By - laws, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Library Faculty Meeting, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Lib - Distance Education Library Support Taskforce, 1997 August (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Library Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1997 November (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Library Faculty Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Library Faculty Offices, Undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Library Faculty Orientation Materials, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Library - Library Faculty Professional Activities Committee, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - University Library Faculty Seminar, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Library Film Service, 1953; 1981 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Library - GEAC,Inc., 1984 January 4-1986 October 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Library, Government Publications Dept., 1963-1970 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Library, Graduate Library of Public Affairs and Policy, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Library - M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Accolades(see: Library), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Library M.E. Grenander Seminar room Lib 220 English Department, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Library Guide, ca. 1956 August-1977 August (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Library Handbook, 1962 June-1974 June (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Library Howard Faculty Group, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Library Hours, ca. 1957 September-1985 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Library Human Relations Area Files, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Library Information Literacy Committee Report, 1993 May (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Library Information Packets, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Library, Information Retrieval, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Library - Information Retrieval, Minutes, 1977 August 31-1978 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Library - Information Retrieval, Minutes, 1979 January 24-1983 April 26 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Library - Interactive Media Center, 1989 November 27-1999 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Library LCS, ca. 1973 January 9-1982 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Library Learning Resources Center, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Library Instruction Unit, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Library - Management Information System, Undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Library Millionth Volume Celebration, 1981-1983; Undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Library: Millionth Volume Celebration, 1982 August (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Library Mission and Objectives Statement, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Library - Monographic Acquisitions Dept., Annual Report 1997 - 78, 1977-1978 May 31 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Library New York State Library, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Library Non - Print Services, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Library Organization Chart, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Library - Organization Charts, 1967-1973; Undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Library - Organization Charts, 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Library - Organizational Analysis of the SUNYA Library, 1976 May 5-1976 May 28 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Library - Library Orientation, ca. 1972-1975 November 4 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Library Performance Evaluation, 1976 March 16-1980 December 15 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Library Periodicals Current Display, 1975 November-1978 January (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Library Periodicals, Current Display, 1978 February-1979 February; Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Library Periodicals Department, ca. 1965 October-1984 August (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Library Periodicals, User Survey, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Library Five Year Plan, ca. 1984 December-1984 December (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Library Floor Plans, ca. 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Library: File Service Catalog, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Library Five Year Plan, 1981 December-1983 December (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Library, Hawley, Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Library Personnel Office, ca. 1970 October 23-1979 September 28 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Library Personnel Office, 1979 October 3-1985 December 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Library, Pierce, ca. 1967 October 5-1971 January 8 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Library, Planning and Operational Support Division, 1981 March 2-1982 November 3 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Library - Planning and Resource Development, Annual Report, ca. 1981 June 1-1984 June 30 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Library Policy Group Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Library Portraits, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Library - Procurement Department, Annual Report, 1971-1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Library - Procurement Department, Annual Report, 1978 July 1-1979 November (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Library Programs, 1978 November 17-1984 October 5 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Library Promotion and Continuing Appointment, 1974 May 20-1980 January 8 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Library Promotion and Continuing Appointment, 1979 January 8-1984 April 2 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Library Promotion and/or Continuing Appointment, ca. 1968 September-1974 April 30 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Library Public Policy Program at SUNYA, Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Library, Quality of Library Life Report, 1982 March 30-1982 December 6 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Library - Readers Services Division, ca. 1967 August 28-1970 June 7 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Library - Recognition Luncheon, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Library - Records Department, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Library, Reference And Bibliographic Development Services, Meetings, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Library - Reference and Bibliographic Development Services, Memoranda, Undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Library - Reference and Bibliographic Development Services, Merger Plan, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Library - Reference and Collection Development Services, Annual Report, 1978 July 13-1979 July 18 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Library - Reference and Collection Development Services, Annual Report, 1980-1981 May 31 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Library - Reference and Collection Development Services, Annual Report, 1980 August 9-1981 May 31 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Library - Reference and Collection Development Services, Coordinators Meetings, 1978 September 6-1982 March 23 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Library - Reference and Collection Development Services, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978 June 20-1979 September 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Library - Reference and Collection, Development Services, Meetings, 1977 November 9-1979 December 19 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Library - Reference and Collection, Development Services, Meetings, 1980 January 9-1982 March 24 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Library - Reference and Collection Development Services, Three Year Plan, 1978 November 21 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Library - Reference Services Department, Meeting Minutes, 1974 September 26 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Library - Reference Services Division Annual Report, 1982 July 23-1983 July 18 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Library - Reference Services Division Annual Report, 1984 August 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Library - Reference Services Division Annual Report, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Library - Reference Services Division Coordinators' Meeting, 1982 April 14-1986 March 11 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Library - Reference Services Division - Faculty Meetings, ca. 1980 July 22-1985 October 16 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Library - Reference Services Division, Faculty Meetings, 1982 April 7-1986 April 10 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Library - Reference Services Division - Faculty Meetings, 1985 November 6-1990 August 14 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Library - Research Libraries Group, 1984 October 31-1985 October 21 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Library - Research Services Division and Reference Department Meeting, 1987 September 16 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Library - Research Services Division, Meeting Minutes, 1986 April 1-1986 October 15 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Library - School Library, Undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Library, Research/Study Leaves, Undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Library Reserve Room, ca. 1966-1985 July 8 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Library Rules, ca. 1934 January 28-1985 April 18 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Library - Search Unit/Department, ca. 1967 December 22-1969 August 8 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Library - Seminar for Library Middle Managers, 1982 January 27-1982 October 27 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Library Social Studies Division Ordering, 1964 February (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Library Special Collections, 1972 January 30-1984 January 17 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Library - Status of Librarians, Committee on Salary Questionnaire, ca. 1968 October-1968 November 20 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Library - Status of Librarians, Committee on Salary Questionnaire, ca. 1968 October-1968 December 4 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Library - Status of Librarians, Committee on Salary Questionnaire, ca. 1968 December 10-1969 April 12 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Library - Special Services, ca. 1965-1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Library - Staff Organization of the University, 1967 January-1970 August 21 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Library Strategic Plan, 1989-1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Library Student Advisors, Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Library Systems Development, ca. 1972 December 4-1982 May 28 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Library Systems Development, Annual Report, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Library Systems Development, 1982 June 1-1986 January 9 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Library Systems Development, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Library - Taskforce on Staff Concerns Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Library - Teacher Education Development Service Research Library, ca. 1975 January-1982 June 30 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Library, Technical Services Annual Reports, 1970 January 16-1981 July 24 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Library, Technical Services Annual Reports, 1982 July 8-1984 June 30 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Library, Technical Services, Miscellaneous, ca. 1970 September 30-1985 January 18 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Library - Technical Services Minutes, 1973 May 10-1984 December 3 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Library Telephone Directory, ca. 1967 August 1-1986 March 26 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Library Three Year Plan, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Library - Term Renewal, 1972 November 30-1983 May 24 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Library, Tours, 1976 January 15-1982 August (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Library UNI, Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Library University Professions, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Library University Senate, 1973 April 3-1974 October 10 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Library Update, 1989 September-1998 September (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Life Long Learners, 1985 March 7 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Life Sciences Research Building Dedication, 2004 October 13 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Liga Filipina, 1995 February 1 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Lincoln Park Pool, 1939; 1941 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Linguistic Colloquium, 1975-1976 February 16 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Linguistics Program, 1975 June 4-1978 June 20 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Linguistics Syllabus, 1990 September (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Lite Sense Program, The, Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - "Literacy and Literature in a Multicultural Society" Fourth Gutenberg Conference, sponsored by Center for Writing and Literacy & Center for Literature Teaching and Learning, 1991 March 1-1991 March 2 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Literate Thinking, Undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Living off Campus, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Logo - Great Dane, 1994 April 28 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Long Range Planning Task Force, 1972 June 28-1973 March 1 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Lovenheim Prize - Newburger, Leah, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Luncheon, Employee Recognition, 2001 November 27 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Luso - Brazilian Club, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Lutheran Campus Ministry, 1976 September 24-1986 March (Box 21, Folder 39)
- M, 1872-2015; 13
  - Magic Club, 1977 September 29 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Mail and Messenger Service, ca. 1972 March 13-1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Maintenance of Roads and Grounds Report, State University of New York at Albany. State University Construction Fund, 1965 October (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Management Department, ca. 1968 March-1987 March (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Management Team, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Maps of Capital District Area, ca. 1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Maps of SUNYA, ca. 1963 June-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Marching Band, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Marcia Brown Research Room Dedication, 2001 October 23 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Marketing Department, 1973 September-1987 March (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Mascot, 1957 March 5-1965 May 14 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Black History Month Luncheon, 1987 February 23-2001 February 15 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Master Plan, 1964-1973 February 28 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Master Plan, 1973 March 15-1975 April 16 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Mater Plan, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Master Theses, 1934 June-1937 June (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - MBA Program, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - McIlwaine Fund, ca. 1965 June 2 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Measles Outbreak, 1987/02/16 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Medallion of the University (see also President's Medallion), ca. 2001 December 18-2004 September 22 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1979 February 28-1983 January (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Meissler, Scott, ca. 1997 March 26-1997 December 11 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Metro - 2000, ca. 1981 May 17 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Meyerson,Martin - (SUNY Buffalo President) Inauguration Coverage Sample, 1967 May 29 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corporation, 1987 July (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Middle Earth, 1985 May 30 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Middle States Accreditation, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Milne 200 Friezes, ca. 1940-2011 May 23 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Milne 200 (Milne School Library) Friezes, 1929-1932 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Milne 200 Lithgow Murals, 1932 October 28-2012 February 1 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Milne Hall, Undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Milne School Booklet for Class of 1965 R., 2015 September (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Milne School Lawsuit - Rhunette Bates et. Al. vs. SUNY College Education at Albany (New York State Commission Against Discrimination), ca. 1961-2009 October 14 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Milne School Logo From Milne Records, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Minerva, Undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Minerva, 1956-1987 (Box 22, Folder 35)